I love thee with the breath, smiles,
tears of all my life.
And if God choose, I shall love thee
better after death.
Yeah, I ain't never going back,
never.
Control,
this is Bird One.
Suspect is continuing on I-78 southbound.
Road ahead is clear.
Copy, Bird One.
Highway units, maintain distance.
Control, suspect is coming in hot.
Roadblock, report status.
Over.
Copy.
Traffic detoured.
Roadblock in position and ready to lay
strips.
Feeling right at home.
Guess we should have blocked the on-ramp,
eh Sarge?
James
Tilton, commanding Arkansas State Police
Highway Patrol Division.
How do you do, Major?
Been better, thanks for asking.
Am I speaking to a Ryan Flanagan?
Fang.
Did you say Fang?
Roger that.
Well Fang, you are
driving a stolen vehicle far in
excess of my beloved
state's posted speed limit.
Firm grasp of the glaringly obvious.
You're senior command, all right.
After fleeing a crime scene in Kentucky,
I've been told that
you've been quite busy.
Wanna tell me what happened?
Did you call to list everything I already
know, Major?
Cause that'll get old real quick.
Well my hope is to resolve this situation
peaceably before anybody gets hurt.
Is there anybody that you'd like to speak
with?
To help us fix this?
You got a wife, right?
Down in Kentucky?
Ex-wife.
Tara?
I was a Marine with 2nd L.A.R.
in Sangin.
Then in the interest of full disclosure,
you should know that I consider all
Jarheads to be knuckle-dragging
cave-dwellers.
I don't necessarily disagree.
What branch were you, Fang?
This conversation has reached its
expiration date.
Besides, guys like us don't get justice,
we get forgotten.
Please, please, don't hang up.
I'm really scared that bad things are
gonna happen if we don't figure this out.
Bad things always happen, Major.
Regardless of how much the shitheads in
charge think they have figured out.
Another beautiful day in paradise,
hey boys?
Put in their hands thy bruising irons of
wrath.
Captain, would you stop Wiz from quoting
Shakespeare?
He makes the rest of us feel illiterate.
I'll never dampen our young man's
intellectual fire.
Well then, I should be able to quote
Hustler's Foreword.
You do you, big fella.
Richard touched Carla's erogenous zone
with a bionic tongue.
Hey Captain, then I should be allowed to
sing The Man in Black.
I'm officially a kindergarten teacher.
There is a house in New Orleans.
They call the rides.
It's a one-on-one, one-on-one,
one-on-one, one-on-one.
Where many a poor boy to destruction have
gone.
Hey guys, that's not in the brochure.
.
Can we do an orbit?
Roger that.
They're talking about us.
RPG right!
RPG down.
No fast kick ass.
RPG right!
Mayday.
Blissey 2-6.
Going down.
No comms.
Brace!
How may I help you, Todd?
Todd's... Todd's gone.
How would you like to be addressed?
Fang.
How may I help you, Fang?
Is this like, uh, Siri?
I'm Helene.
Digital Automative Concierge.
Designed to make driving more comfortable.
Handy.
Let's see... Helene, uh, find
me a falafel restaurant in...
Denmark.
One moment while I look that up.
You were right.
First Special Forces.
Fort Campbell.
Three tours.
Bronze Star and Purple Heart.
The Persian Prince in Copenhagen is the
top reviewed on Yelp.
Gina.
Anna S.
from Hamburg gives the Persian Prince four
stars.
Quote, I closed my eyes and thought I woke
up in Amman.
Unquote.
Did you... did you translate that review
from Danish?
German.
His nickname is Fang.
Special Ops guys only use these nicknames.
Thanks.
And he ran Jungle Warfare School for two
years.
I heard guys had to kill a crocodile with
their bare hands to graduate that school.
Major.
The FBI is here.
Of course they are.
What is the length of the Trans Siberian
Railroad?
5478 miles, Fang.
How about the most effective way to train
a house cat.
To use the toilet.
One moment while I look that up.
When you find it, could you email the link
to my ex wife?
Certainly, Fang.
What is your ex wife's email address?
How does a marriage fail when both people
love each other deeply?
Stop.
Stop saying that.
You're not happy.
And neither am I.
I know I've had some regression,
but I'm better.
You never sleep.
You're popping Xanax and Valium like it's
candy.
And you're angry.
You're still so angry.
And then you stop going to therapy.
You tell them you need a little break.
That's not how it works.
Ryan, I love you with all my heart,
with all my soul.
But I can't... I can't fix you.
And I'm completely worn out from trying.
I don't know who I am anymore.
I want a divorce.
Maybe.
Hey.
Special Agent Bridges.
Special Agent Heller.
Thank y'all for coming down.
But I think we got it covered.
Understood, Major.
With a homicide investigation.
Whoa, whoa.
Homicide?
Kentucky never gave us any details of
that.
And we suspect that he's armed with a
murder weapon.
I'm sorry to interrupt, Fang.
But I need to inform you that you are
running on the vehicle's
reserve fuel supply.
Oh, come on.
Screw you, Todd.
I'm unable to address this request.
No, not... How long
before I'm out of fuel?
At your current speed, reserve fuel will
be exhausted in 3.4 minutes.
How far is the closest airport?
Memorial Field in Hot Springs is 4.6 miles
northwest of your current location.
Can I make it on reserve fuel?
At a much reduced speed.
Would you like me to book you a plane
ticket out of Hot Springs?
Major, suspect has exited the interstate.
Control, this is Bird One.
We are terminating aerial pursuit.
Suspect heading west of Hot Springs.
What the hell?
Protected airspace for Memorial Field.
Smart man.
What's he... he's trying to fly out?
Get Hot Springs PD on the car.
And alert TSA.
Already taken care of.
Proceed west on Crane Avenue for three and
a half miles.
Then turn left on Wells Avenue.
Your destination will be on the right.
At this speed, will we make it?
Yes.
Recalculating route.
All
available units, 1080 in progress.
Control, suspect entered first junkyard on
Wells Avenue.
I am unable to identify your current
location.
Don't beat yourself up.
At nine percent.
And get that car's cell phone tracked.
This report doesn't track with its
history.
It's not exactly painting a clear picture.
Clear as mud.
You gotta hear his side.
He doesn't give himself up.
His side won't matter.
We've got a bomb on the way in.
The vehicle's reserve supply has been
exhausted.
Son of a...
We've got this.
We're leaving you alone.
We have to go.
You're construir this
place personally- Hey.
Hey.
Good morning.
How you doing?
Good.
Ain't she a peach?
Ain't she just.
Fill her up, please.
Yes, sir.
Bet that'll get you there quick.
Say that again.
How long you had her?
Since this morning.
She set you back a pretty penny?
Surprisingly reasonable.
Keep the change.
Thanks.
Hey, um, I'm gonna let you finish up
yourself.
Good choice.
You mean Big Head Edward?
Yes.
Yeah, he's another there.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Um, is your friend still coming?
He's already here.
To whiz on the anniversary of his death.
To whiz.
Whiz.
Look at his eyes.
Look at his wrists.
Stay with me.
I before you.
I before you left.
Stay with me.
We got you.
Yeah.
Attaboy.
Delphine filed for divorce.
Again?
Yeah, I believe that's a unit record for
busted marriages, right?
Three, two, and one?
I thought she said she talked to the
councilor and she was locked in.
Well, apparently her position has evolved.
The snake eaters make lethal killers.
Shit husbands.
To all wives whose marriage vows amount to
less than a teaspoon of Bob Tant piss.
Tara's engaged.
Says she's too old to be alone.
Who's the fucker?
Some rich, newer folk freak.
Todd.
Something or other.
I never met a Todd.
I didn't want a punch in the throat.
To all rich, Louisville
pricks with the name of Todd
something or other who
we'd like to punch in the throat.
You ever just want to go out in a blaze of
glory?
Every day.
Move fast and kick ass.
Pardon me, gentlemen.
What happened?
Hey.
Just promise me you're not gonna get into
it with him.
Who?
Todd.
He did this to you?
Has he hit you before?
Never.
Did you call the police?
Half the force is fucking golf buddies.
So listen to me.
Just let it go.
I called you.
I wanted you to hear it from me first.
I already broke it off with him.
He's dead to me.
And that's done.
Okay?
I promise.
I won't hurt him.
That's my sister.
Hey, hon.
The doctor says I'm gonna be okay.
Overnight, though.
Uh, yeah, but I want you to get my shit
out of this place.
Can you go there in the morning?
He'll be at work all day.
No, but...
Oh.
Right.
Okay.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm sure.
I can wait.
I guess I can wait.
Thanks.
Hey, I can do it.
Mm-mm.
What?
I'll have it over first thing.
In and out.
He won't even be there.
Right?
Ah...
Oh...
All right.
Just because he loves you.
Come on.
Come on, dude.
Trust me.
You want this.
Ryan.
What are you doing here?
Getting Tara's stuff.
Okay.
Tara's not going anywhere, pal.
You consider yourself lucky.
You're not locked up.
Or worse.
What's worse is breaking and entering.
I'm just standing my ground.
Yeah.
Hey, hey, hey.
Yeah, I know what you are.
What you're capable of.
Todd.
Put the gun down.
I just need to get Tara's stuff and leave.
Stop moving!
On your knees!
Now!
God damn it.
Hands behind your head!
Hey, I called the police when I saw your
shit box in my driveway.
They're on their way.
Put the gun down, and I'll leave.
I said on your fucking-Oh, fuck.
Where is she?
Hey, hey!
Hey!
Shut up, you son of a bitch!
I need directions into Texas using only
surface streets.
Checkout time, boys.
Grab some gear.
It's not late.
Sir, we've regained air pursuit.
What about ground?
En route.
Should we alert Texas Highway Patrol?
Unfortunately, yes.
Hey, honey.
You need to come see the TV.
According to police, this chase began in
Kentucky.
KJHX2 Texas has learned that the driver of
the stolen red Shelby is Ryan Flanagan,
former Army Special Forces officer,
who served three combat tours in
Afghanistan and has no previous criminal
record.
Apparently, Flanagan fled
the crime scene in Kentucky,
which we are still trying
to get information on.
KJHX2 Texas...
Hey, tanker.
Captain needs us.
Suspect.
That's one word for it.
I'm surprised you and your posse didn't
just lynch him in the town square.
Suspect crosses that line.
It'll end the way we see fit.
We?
You mean you.
Have you even read his bio, Walter?
The crime scene report?
Flanagan was a highly decorated vet.
How do we know this wasn't self-defense?
Well, I ain't no college boy like you,
Jimbo.
But in my experience, a person who's
innocent, they don't run.
Certainly not at 100 miles per hour.
May we share your video feed, please?
Why, certainly.
Why don't you all sit back, relax,
and enjoy the show.
Where'd you get this?
Does it matter?
So this bird is stolen.
Hey, I prefer to characterize the status
of this aircraft as borrowed.
You would characterize it as borrowed.
What would they characterize it as?
How many miles to the state line,
Helene?
7.1, Flan.
Unidentified caller.
Hello?
Am I speaking to Captain Flanagan?
Who's this?
Laura Coates, producer.
Sarah Anders, CNN.
May she speak with you live on the air?
Wow.
Go ahead, Sarah.
I am live with Captain Ryan Flanagan,
former U.S.
Army Special Forces.
I was a captain once, Laura.
But at the moment, I'm just
an old fart who dreams of
racial harmony, religious
accord, and bargain doughnuts.
We are speaking as you continue to evade
police in a high-speed jet.
If I'd only just returned those library
books.
You want to tell us about what happened
back in Kentucky, Captain?
Not in the least.
Were you acting in self-defense?
Aren't we all?
From an evolutionary standpoint,
I mean.
Would you like to tell us why you're
fleeing from the police?
Because they're chasing me.
Have you considered surrendering?
I thought I did for a second, but then I
realized I just had to pee.
Captain Flanagan.
Is there anything you'd like to say to
anyone that might be watching?
Anyone you'd like to talk to?
Yeah.
A guy called Wiz.
I'm sorry I couldn't save you.
Wish it had been me instead of you,
kiddo.
The destination is 200 yards ahead.
Who's in the car with you, Captain?
You can go wherever you want.
An easy mind will take you there.
Bring me along as your ambulance fares.
Don't lose heart, my brother.
The rumbled road you'd walk.
Like a bird traveling light.
From high above for a better sight.
They're coming for us.
We got you.
We're going home, Wiz.
We're going home.
We're going home, come on.
Come on, Wiz.
We're going home.
I
will come sing your song.
When days break and stay too long.
Overwatch, do you have eyes on?
Control, Overwatch, no shot.
Arkansas HP in line of fire.
Have Arkansas HP pull back.
Gun, gun, gun.
Control, Overwatch.
Suspect has retrieved the pistol.
I repeat, suspect is armed.
Swat element is moving.
Hold SWAT with the arm.
We're receiving fragmented
reports from the Texas
Highway Patrol who
were forming the roadblock.
The Captain Flanagan is armed.
As you can see from our footage,
the vehicle is stopped in front of the
Texas roadblock with Arkansas State Police
blocking its escape from behind.
And again, according to the police, the
driver, Ryan Flanagan,
is now holding a gun.
Hello, one more spot.
Did you email me a cat toilet training
link?
Technically, my stolen car did.
Hey, I'm gonna need you to come home and
help me with that.
Can't, sorry.
You alone?
Howdy, boys.
Why don't you clear out?
Give me a moment alone, but my ex.
Please.
Yes, sir.
Okay, they're gone.
Ryan, listen to me.
You've got to give yourself up right now.
I can't do that.
Yes, you can.
You've got to.
It's stopped shitting around time.
I will never be captured again.
What happened to Liz was not your fault.
I couldn't save her.
Yeah, nobody could have, baby.
I was his commander.
It was my responsibility.
I'm to blame.
Are you hearing me?
It's not yours to carry.
So, what do you do now?
Oh, escape.
Evaded.
The usual.
But you can't keep running unless you've
got someplace to go.
Oh, I got a place to go.
Okay.
Maybe then you drive.
You drive.
Drive as fast as you can.
Block all access points.
Rebuilt for off-road.
Recalculating route.
Where are you going, Major?
We are going to Texas.
Are you sure that's a good idea?
I'm certain it's not.
I am unable to identify your current
location.
I had a feeling you'd say that.
You said it, but didn't you?
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Looks
like our epic journey together has come to
an end.
I'm sorry to hear that, Fang.
Our journey continues, Selene.
I'm delighted to hear that, Fang.
Shit.
We are now into the
fifth hour of this chase
and roughly 30 miles
into northeastern Texas.
CNN has learned that the driver,
former U.S.
Army Captain Ryan Flanagan,
was a decorated Green
Beret, wounded multiple
times during combat operations.
He'll never turn himself in.
Sounded like you two still have a
connection.
Why'd you divorce him?
Oh, let me see.
Thinking back on it...
Hmm.
None of your fucking business.
Look, we need all the help we can,
and time is not on our side.
Yeah, you mean on his side.
The FBI continues to issue
brief general statements
that they are closely
monitoring the situation...
Okay, when he came back that last time,
things were really good for a while.
We were older, things felt more clear, but
something happened when he was over there.
He was captured.
And he was broken.
Do you understand what he sacrificed?
Hey.
What's between us?
The Pentagon has confirmed that Captain
Ryan Flanagan, a Bronze Star recipient and
multiple Purple Heart honoree,
was honorably discharged in 2005,
having served with distinction.
Wiz's real name was Wade Melvie.
He was a Master Sergeant in Captain
Flanagan's Special Forces Unit.
In their final tour in Afghanistan,
their helicopter was shot down,
and the unit was captured.
During their escape, Melvie was killed.
Captain Flanagan and the
surviving members of the unit
served as pallbearers at
Sergeant Melvie's funeral.
The saying, never leave a man behind,
is a deeply ingrained principle in the
military, especially within Special
Forces.
This sentiment is a powerful
cultural force within the
Armed Services and fosters a
strong sense of responsibility.
It appears that application is still
standing even in this complex scenario.
Does Arkansas already miss me,
Major Tilton?
This is Major Walter Pope, Commander of
Texas Highway Patrol.
I stand corrected.
Thanks for the welcome mat back there,
Major.
Well, now, Captain
Flanagan, y'all better stop this
nonsense or things are gonna
get a whole lot worse for you.
Sounds like a threat, and I tend to
respond aggressively to those.
In my state, when a suspect
resists arrest in a vehicle, law
enforcement's within their
rights to open fire on that vehicle.
Texas, where the entire state sports a
collective hard-on.
Every time a gun is fired.
Well, as I'm sure you know from combat,
whenever rifle fire is involved,
stray bullets are always a possibility.
Listen to me, you inbred dung farmer.
I've been ducking small arms fire most of
my life.
So if you can rip yourself away from
scraping off roadkill along the interstate
long enough to join the hunt, please,
bring it on.
No.
I will, Flanagan.
I surely will.
Call ended.
Helene, can you make the car's phone
untraceable?
Certainly, Fang.
The vehicle's phone tracking has gone
dead, Major.
Why aren't we tracking his personal cell?
Haven't been able to.
He must have a burner or an unplugged
phone.
He's smart.
We'll keep trying.
Tell Swat.
By the before you...
by before you let them.
Is
that a God damn news chopper?
I can't confirm, sir.
Norm.
Give me a still frame to that shot.
Bingo.
Tell Swat.
If that's the one, That bird is impeding
them.
They are clear to engage.
Sir, should we try to make contact first?
I mean, the entire country is watching.
We are about to make contact, Captain.
Tanker, where are you?
Above you.
You're flying that gazelle?
Munches, like a madman.
Hey, buddy.
Hey, pal.
Hey, I don't want you guys getting mixed
up in this.
A little late for that, Captain.
We'll keep the birds off you for as long
as we can.
Take evasive maneuvers.
That's all I've been doing.
Then I guess take more evasive maneuvers.
Gotta go, brother.
Helene, what's the closest city?
One moment while I look that up.
Where the hell's the suspect?
You ordered a SWAT to engage.
I, but, sir... I don't give a good
goddamn if the cameras see it.
That's felony obstruction.
Tyler, population 100,223.
I think they're green-lit.
I'm gonna need you to find a certain kind
of establishment there.
Somebody get a visual on the suspect.
Kick-ass!
The Special Forces are often described as
the most powerful force in the world.
But what's said by military planners is
the tip of the spear in combat operations.
A recent VA study published in the New
England Journal of Medicine found that
special operations soldiers suffer from
PTSD after combat
at nearly twice the rate.
Shows of support for
Flanagan are appearing across
all social media platforms,
urging police restraint.
In any efforts to apprehend him.
We're seeing scores of
viral posts from all over
the country, from veterans
to college students.
Hi.
Good afternoon.
You all do paint jobs?
Yeah.
What does that cost, typically?
Running a one-day special.
Free.
For anybody.
You shed blood for this country.
Let's get that leg taken care of.
Follow me.
Munch, is that an airport?
They can't follow.
Dude, I think we're hit.
Control, Black Hawk 7.
Target neutralized.
Sending ground units to Walters Airfield.
Hey, Tanker, you all right?
Yeah, I'm okay.
I don't want to mention to you how much I
hate jail.
We're not out of the game yet.
You got a credit card on you?
Wow.
You took the liberty of changing out your
plates for the clean Texas Tech.
Sure as hell ain't gonna hide this dragon
for too much longer.
It'll have to do.
I'll take you to jail.
A buddy of mine served in them.
He helped you out.
I can't thank you enough.
We might have been in different wars.
We're still brothers.
You travel safe now.
Oh Lord, I don't want to die in Texas.
Come on, Tex!
Sing it with me!
We're the deer of the antelope plain.
How in the hell did we lose him?
It's impossible.
Last list of registration, ma'am.
The Kentucky State Police just released
the name of the victim at the crime scene.
Captain Flanagan fled.
He was Todd Ferris, a 58-year-old
prominent defense attorney in Louisville
who has defended many high-profile
clients, including the ex-governor.
The Louisville Courier released a story on
their website about 20 minutes ago citing
an arrest report from 2004 charging Todd
Ferris with a multi-million dollar real
estate fraud scheme that was later
dropped.
The story goes on to say...
Are you okay?
Hey, are you okay?
I've been ringing you.
Tell me everything's okay.
I'm fine.
Uh-uh.
I can hear it in your voice.
Don't bullshit me, Ryan.
Tara.
I'm good.
Where are you?
Tyler, Texas.
Which is charming, by the way.
Oh my God.
I was so worried that...
The cameras lost you for six hours.
Where are you?
At my sister's.
Also charming, by the way.
Um...
Tell me something.
Was it self-defense?
Feels like everything I do is
self-defense.
That's not an answer, baby.
I did everything I could not to hurt him.
I promise.
And he shot me in the leg.
But it was him or me, Tara.
I swear.
Then I'm glad it was you.
Hey, been thinking a lot about that beach.
Beach?
What beach?
The one near Cancun.
Remember?
Oh.
That beach.
Locals called it La Mongosta.
Yeah.
The mongoose.
Why do they call it that again?
No snakes.
As I recall, we did some epic boning on
that beach.
Indeed we did.
You should go back.
You mean it?
Yeah.
It's my retirement plan.
Okay.
I'll tell you what.
You get to the mongoose, and we'll take
you from there.
It's always been you.
And only you.
My whole life.
And you for me.
Yeah, just put it in park.
Morning, Tim.
What's happening?
Roy.
Looking for that runaway vet.
He robbed Fort Knox.
I just work here.
Making your run down to San Antonio?
Per usual.
All right.
Have a good one then.
Thanks, Roy.
Still hurting?
I'll be okay.
The guy shot me back in Kentucky.
In case you were wondering.
I wasn't.
I'll let the state police know I seen you.
Crossing into Oklahoma.
Get a couple of dozen brother vet trucks
to call it in, too.
By the end of the day, your mares will be
hunting you in Alaska.
Thank you, brother.
I was a POW in NAMM for three and a half
years.
Guards used to hurt me.
Everywhere you could figure.
Whenever I can help out a brother vet,
I feel like I'm hurting them guards back.
Just a little.
That's Shelby, old hon.
He's just crossed into New Mexico.
I seen that Shelby.
Near Shreveport.
Yeah, that fan guy all over the news is
walking down the strip in Vegas.
Got a call.
He's headed back to Kentucky.
That's horseshit.
He's getting help.
From who?
Don't matter.
They all think he's John Wayne.
What?
Ditch the Shelby and hide now?
This money ain't the hiding type.
Where would you go?
You just murdered somebody.
Where's he been headed all along?
Move everybody south.
I'm gonna lock up that border tighter than
my stepson's search history.
I got you now, you son of a bitch.
You and me again, Helene.
I am pleased to hear that, Fang.
We could have been something, darling.
If you weren't, you know, an appliance.
I'm unable to.
Never mind.
Hey, where are you now?
Texas, I'm guessing.
But given Munch's navigational skills,
it could easily be Wyoming.
She's slow, but damn, she's maneuverable.
Bears on you.
All clear for now.
Where you headed?
The Mongoose.
The barn?
The beach.
A few hundred clicks south.
So?
Craving an authentic margarita.
Care to join me, boys?
Hell yeah.
I was looking for a new place to retire.
Yeah, same here.
Helene, I need you to find me the three
nearest crossing points into Mexico.
Captain Flanagan is making all of us who
serve feel empowered.
How so?
Well, just like the rest of us,
he's fighting against a system that all
too often misjudges the veterans,
and he's blind to their suffering.
Thank you.
Veterans organizations from across the
United States have publicly expressed
solidarity with Captain Flanagan,
building to the already massive wave of
support that is currently sweeping the
nation.
He's set in a The destination
is 200 yards ahead.
Thank you, Felin.
But we're gonna need to move on to option
two.
Calculating route.
Is anyone ready right now?
We'll be right out.
Cool.
Isn't it a pleasure
to see you again?
Suspect traveling east on Highland,
3 miles west, 83.
We found it, sir.
East on Highland before 83.
Be advised, suspect's
vehicle has now changed
its colors to black and its tags to Texas.
Hotel, Lima, Victor, Papa, 0905.
I repeat, color is now black with Texas
tags.
Get air pursuit to that position and all
available units.
230 for a pit maneuver, moving in now.
Come on, come on.
Control, this is 230.
I've lost visual of the suspect,
now heading southbound on 83.
There's dung farmers about to put you in
the world of shit.
Status on the roadblocks?
In position, sir.
7-8-1, I'm saying suspect.
35, sir, back in 8-1.
I see
on our live feed, Captain
Flanagan has changed the
color of his vehicle and is
continuing to evade police.
We've received reports of elevated police
presence along the southern border,
indicating that law
enforcement is preparing
for an attempt to flee into Mexico.
Re-calculating route.
Suspect has exited the 83 heading
southwest.
They tipped him off.
Well, he's got to turn back if he still
wants to cross over.
No way he pulls that off.
This is our chance to block him in against
the Gulf.
Bring in all units.
Option 3 for border crossing is 44.3 miles
back to the southwest.
Your turn is not a possibility.
Call the governor's office.
Have them scramble the Air National Guard.
Sir.
Everybody on point.
CNN has learned that Texas Highway Patrol
Major Walter Pope, the man leading the
effort to apprehend Flanagan, has faced
three separate state internal
investigations for excessive force,
none of which led to criminal charges.
CNN has reached out to Major Pope for
comment.
Status on units.
Units converging in L.A.
I
need to inform you,
Flan, that the front left
tire of the vehicle is
damaged beyond repair.
Oh, really?
Control, 217.
Suspect stationary on roundabout.
Car at United Route 151 joining.
Clear the airspace.
Sir, this is Control.
Texas law enforcement has ordered local
news to clear the airspace.
So we will not be able to bring you live
coverage of what is about to unfold.
Ground units cleared to engage at will.
Step out of the vehicle with your hands
up.
Driver, out of the vehicle, now!
Damn!
These bastards again!
Get the SWAT helo up there!
It's back in Tyler.
Well, what about Air National Guard?
Viper 1, this is Control.
Report your position.
Control, this is Viper 1.
I'm 10 Mike Sapp.
Step out of the vehicle!
If you do not comply, we will fire upon
you!
I can see clearly now the rain is gone.
I can see all obstacles in my way.
Gone are the dark clouds that had me
blind.
It's gonna be bright, bright, bright.
It's a shiny day.
Let
me!
I got you, brother.
Bye, Eileen!
Goodbye, Fang.
Where's the National Guard yet?
Should be there by now, sir.
Take him out.
You heard me.
Do it!
Viper 1, this is Control.
You are cleared to engage.
Pete,
you are cleared to engage the target.
What the hell is going on?
Control, my bombs are malfunctioning.
It's time for those margaritas,
boys.
God damn it!
Call in the Coast Guard!
Major Pope, the FBI has jurisdiction.
Those were international waters.
I guess this one didn't end the way you
saw fit.
Huh, Walter?
Yeah.
They're wearing the mask!
I cant't make you look any phews.
We'll finish this.
Take care.
You're gonna have to get us back to the
core tomorrow.
In the big wilderness!
Don't go.
I am losing these margaritas.
There they are.
I'm gonna go to the hospital.
Captain Ryan Flanagan has
escaped capture unscathed, flying
over international waters with
the help of his unit members.